[{"answer": "Well, it's been a chaotic year.", "docId": "111222pmt", "aSentId": 36, "question": "But what do you think?", "qSentId": 35}, {"answer": "ROKAW: I thought it was a good call, frankly.", "docId": "111222pmt", "aSentId": 55, "question": "What did you think of that choice?", "qSentId": 54}, {"answer": "Well, I think it's a very different -- first of all, Occupy Wall Street is not calling for the overthrow of their government.", "docId": "111222pmt", "aSentId": 72, "question": "I mean, is there -- is there a common thread there or are they very different, distinct protests?", "qSentId": 71}, {"answer": "Well, first of all, I was a member of the luckiest generation as my contemporaries -- and we've all agreed that we were the ones who really caught the best wave, because after the war, our parents who had gone through all the trials of the Depression and World War II, then came home to unprecedented working class and middle class prosperity.", "docId": "111222pmt", "aSentId": 93, "question": "What kind of future young Americans going to be facing?", "qSentId": 92}, {"answer": "ROKAW: Well, I frankly I'm a big advocate of as many debates as we can have along primary seasons because you find out about candidates during that time.", "docId": "111222pmt", "aSentId": 177, "question": "What do you make of the way the Republican race is going, the debates in particular?", "qSentId": 176}, {"answer": "Well, I think he has some hopes that he can do that.", "docId": "111222pmt", "aSentId": 190, "question": "And is it unfeasible that someone like him could actually come from a very low base and still win the nomination?", "qSentId": 189}, {"answer": "I mean, what you could have -- judging by the polls at the moment -- you could have Ron Paul winning in Iowa.", "docId": "111222pmt", "aSentId": 216, "question": "If he can do well in Iowa and then at least be in the hunt in New Hampshire, then goes out to South Carolina, and then go to Florida, who knows?", "qSentId": 215}, {"answer": "I didn't have any -- listen, I didn't have anything against -- I have known Donald Trump for a long time.", "docId": "111222pmt", "aSentId": 233, "question": "What did you have against that?", "qSentId": 232}, {"answer": "Well, first of all, I think it's very -- very hard to judge the greatness of a president midterm and that's kind of where we are.", "docId": "111222pmt", "aSentId": 291, "question": "Has he been on balance more of a success than a failure?", "qSentId": 290}, {"answer": "You know, you're not going to trap me into that.", "docId": "111222pmt", "aSentId": 320, "question": "Who do you think has been the most impressive of all of them?", "qSentId": 319}, {"answer": "Well, what I think is -- and I think it's a complex question, by the way.", "docId": "111222pmt", "aSentId": 354, "question": "When you saw President Obama really trying to make it that it had been a victory and it had all been worth it, did you agree with him?", "qSentId": 353}, {"answer": "That was an easier call for the involvement of the American military as part of NATO force.", "docId": "111222pmt", "aSentId": 375, "question": "What do you think about the changing manner in which American military is now deploying itself?", "qSentId": 374}, {"answer": "Well, it's -- war should not be reduced to a semantic exercise of some kind.", "docId": "111222pmt", "aSentId": 397, "question": "Wouldn't it be better to say we're going to tackle terrorism head on, and actually treat Afghanistan, rather than a war, as an anti-terrorism operation?", "qSentId": 396}, {"answer": "I had to trade jackets later with one of my colleague, Mike Besher (ph), because I got to thinking, this is probably going to be on videotape for a long time, and I ought to get dressed up a little more.", "docId": "111222pmt", "aSentId": 422, "question": "Any regrets over the green jacket, Tom, looking back on that?", "qSentId": 421}, {"answer": "Well, unfortunately, I don't want to relive some of them, because the single hardest week I had, and the single hardest day by far, was 9/11.", "docId": "111222pmt", "aSentId": 440, "question": "When you look at all the incredible things that you've witnessed, Tom, over the last few decades, which to you is the standout moment, the one that if you had the chance to relive it and to be there again, you would take?", "qSentId": 439}, {"answer": "Of course.", "docId": "111222pmt", "aSentId": 459, "question": "Are you still a complete news junkie?", "qSentId": 458}]